Ah, found you.
Hey there.
We're missing Jim.
I don't have clothes.
They threw them away.
And the trash?
Oh, that's right.
How could I forget?
They look like they're having so much fun.
I hate them.
We did, didn't we?
And people in cliques are the absolute worst.
Because they made us feel more excluded than we already were.
I hate break time, too.
Yeah, breaks were pretty rough, no doubt.
We can practically hear the whispers now.
It always felt like kids were pointing out how alone we were.
I mean, they weren't wrong.
We hated special events, too.
In fact, I can't remember a single thing we didn't hate in those days.
It sucks.
Nobody needs a loser like me around.
Can I just die?
Um...
I think we should probably hold off on that.
Not much further down the road, we'll make a friend.
He's annoying, though, so heads up.
Then we'll meet a kid with great taste of music, a super sweet girl, and a guy who's as tall as he is kind.
Oh, and a semi-spineless president and his posse, too.
Believe it or not, there are a lot of people who want to be friends with us.
Best of all, we'll eventually meet someone who'll cry for us, and laugh at most of our jokes, and keep us in line when we start acting up.
I promise she's out there.
If that's true, then...
I guess...
What was I just dreaming about?
I wanna see Hori.
Don't let Sober bronier.
Everything has known...
You gotta do what I want...
Don't let...
Like I said...
What happened?
I hinted at this thing here.
Whatever...
Sober Pole...
Can I just be instituted?
How did those peoples jeadum...
Doesn't matter likeなるチャンネル...
You think...
How do you love lol
I guess...
Don't let me tell you...
trying to fight always lots...
You think...
Thank you very much.
The boy I fell in love with is really weak.
And that's not an exaggeration.
Even if the occasion calls for it, he doesn't actually like yelling at people.
A laugh about how bad he is at sports, while secretly wishing he wasn't.
Boys and girls alike can't help but fawn over him, and their adoration makes him happy.
However, it sometimes makes him feel anxious, too.
There's so much he struggles with, and I love him to pieces for it.
Ah! Oh no!
Zenkoku saved me!
There's a spider!
I'm so scared!
Judging from that expression, I'm not the only one.
And yet...
He faced his fears anyway.
Good job.
The boy I love is weak.
But he doesn't let that slow him down.
Although...
Back when we first met, he was almost a completely different person.
That Ayasaki, man.
I am crushing, like, so hard on her.
I never get tired of looking at that cute little face.
I totally get what you mean.
But she's kind of hard to approach.
Like, she thinks she's too good for us or something.
Well, she has ears, so I'm guessing she knows all the guys have the hots for her.
Oh, and her friend Kono sticks out like a sore thumb.
And I mean really sore, because she looks rough next to Ayasaki.
I disagree.
I think they're both pretty average.
Ayasaki's a hottie with a body, and you know it!
Not to me.
They both look normal.
Hey, what were you reading in class just now?
Hmm?
A manga?
Goethe.
Goethe?
Um, what is that?
A renowned German author.
I thought you meant the title at first.
Is it good?
Does your interest mean you like books, too?
I won't have my nose in one like that during class, but yeah, books are awesome.
Like Grimm's fairy tales.
So Snow White type stuff?
Yeah, that's right up my alley.
Hmm.
I brought books for you to borrow.
No way, you did?
There's lots of stories to choose from, so you're bound to like one or two.
Wow, thanks so much!
That looks like it'll be a fun read.
Yep.
Oh, do you enjoy books like these, too?
You're asking me?
I do.
Then, once Ayasaki's finished, you can borrow them as well.
The third story in this collection is really captivating.
It's one of my faves.
Wait, are you positive?
Mm-hmm.
Gosh, thank you!
Sure, don't mention it.
Hmm?
You know, you have great taste!
I like them all.
Good, because they brought more.
Wow, you're like a one-man library.
That's amazing!
How many books do you own?
My parents own most of these.
We have a room filled wall-to-wall with them back home.
That sounds insane!
I wish I could see.
You can, if you want to.
Oh, did I say that?
I didn't mean anything weird!
Yeah, of course.
Neither did I.
It is filled wall-to-wall!
We don't clean this room much.
I'm sorry that it's so dusty.
You okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
I was just trying to pull down this book is all.
I should have asked before I touched, though.
Won't find many books older than that one.
Do you remember the premise?
I think it's about the day before the world ends.
Oh.
As in the whole world or Japan?
I believe it's the whole world.
So they're in panic mode.
If everything was going up in smoke the next day,
most people would probably just lie around and wait for it.
Oh, not me!
I'd spend the whole day blowing through my money,
then load up on desserts!
It's your final day on Earth,
and you're gonna stuff your face?!
There's so much I haven't tried,
so I might as well.
Huh.
Your hair, it's up higher than it usually is, right?
Yeah, I just felt like it.
Nice call. Looks good.
You think so?
Cute people could get away with murder
and look cute doing it.
But I guess you wouldn't get where I'm coming from, huh?
Mind if I borrow you for a second?
Pretty please?
Thanks for lending me these.
I read every last page.
There was no need to rush through them.
I didn't.
They were so entertaining that I couldn't put them down.
And that one book made me realize
how much I don't want the world to end.
What about your big sweets binge?
There are way more important things than sweets
when it's Judgment Day!
So, you know,
he's staring because he has a crush on you.
Okay.
Hey, would it be cool
if I came over to your place again today?
Sure, but...
just to be clear,
you're coming for the books
and not to spend time with only me, right?
You know,
don't want to get the wrong idea.
This is a series you'll totally be into.
It's long, but...
a very satisfying read.
Neat.
I can't wait.
Um,
Sengoku?
Hmm?
I, uh...
kinda, sorta...
had a question.
Then shoot.
Okay, then...
it's...
hypothetical.
Hmm?
If you knew without a doubt
the world was gonna end tomorrow,
what would you honestly do?
What?
Like in the book?
Well, that inspired it.
Yeah.
I would confess
that I like you.
Uh...
Then I dissolve
into space dust.
The end.
That's supposed to be a joke?
No.
I was serious.
Forget I said anything.
What are you embarrassed for?
Who says that I'm embarrassed?
Because I'm not.
It isn't very nice to lie.
What reason would I have to lie to you?
Just let it go.
Wanna know how I know?
Your face is almost completely red.
Looks cute.
Whatever you say.
Guess what?
You're not alone in feeling that way.
Remy likes you too.
Oh.
The thing is,
I like you a lot, Remy.
Thanks for loaning me this.
Huh!
You read the whole thing in a day?
I finished studying early,
so I had some extra time.
Impressive.
And your thoughts?
Managed to squeeze any tears out?
No, but it was alright.
He was lying.
He cried like a baby while reading it.
When we met,
he didn't let the opinions of others sway him.
I loved him then,
and I love him now.
His weak points,
his inability to lie,
his perseverance,
I love every part of him.
So, um,
you're training to be a beautician?
Uh,
I found some unopened bottles of nail polish
while I was cleaning my room,
and I thought this color
would look good on you.
I see.
What?
Oh, no.
Must resist all temptation.
Think of how mad she'd be.
Okay,
time for the other foot.
But...
Mia Morda,
stop daydreaming
and give me your...
My foot's on your head
because...
I thought...
I might level up.
Huh?
That was a joke!
You're always messing with me,
so I figured I'd try messing with you,
but I'm an idiot!
And it's really sorry, idiot!
It's not that big a deal,
so calm down.
I'm not upset with you,
I'm just a little surprised.
I mean,
you're constantly going off
on Shindo and Sawada,
but when you're around me,
you're like the paragon of courtesy.
So is all that a front?
Are you...
faking it for me?
It's real!
How I act around you...
is real.
Oh.
What's wrong?
Would you...
prefer if I yelled a bunch
and head-butted you
like you were one of them?
What?
No way!
Damn!
Come on and move your ass,
Kyoko!
The hell'd you think
you're talking to,
you dumb bitch?
But...
hot roleplay.
Huh?
Good morning, Miyamura!
Sup!
You fellas doing good?
Not that I care.
Okay.
What do we have here?
You seriously still listening
to this crap?
They're all bobs,
but damn.
Huh?
The hell?
What's going on?
Hey, Miyamura?
Could I borrow
your Math B textbook, please?
You need to get your shit together
as soon as possible,
but I feel generous today.
Blame!
Who is that guy?
How should I know?
I'm as clueless as you are!
Something you want to share
with the class?
Kill me.
Eh.
I take it
Her Royal Highness
the Ice Queen
asked you to act hard
if you're uncomfortable
behaving this way,
then tell her.
Good morning!
Man out, son!
Or I'll beat you
senseless till you do!
Stop making this my problem!
Aw, shame it was
so tough for you.
I guess your dominating side
will only live on
in my dreams.
Well, maybe I'll give you
time to forget about it
then try again.
Really?
Oh man, I can't wait!
Peace.
See you later!
Kay!
Wait, I'm almost positive
the physics room
isn't open during lunchtime.
Hmm?
Oh, shoot.
I think you're right.
What a pain.
I'll have to wait
till after the break
to drop these off,
so can you let our teacher know?
Want me to go?
Nah, I got it.
Excuse me.
Do you have a moment?
Me?
Huh.
I know I said
I'd wait till she forgot,
but I doubt she thinks
I'll try anything right now.
What kind of dirtbag thing
could I say or do
to make her happy, though?
Hmm.
Oh!
Guess what, Miyamorta?
Who exactly do you think
you're talking to,
you frickin' airhead?
I ain't your friend,
so back the hell off
and shut the hell up!
Huh?
Ah!
I'm sorry, Hori,
but I just can't do this,
so don't expect
a repeat of that.
I've never been more lost
in the maze
that is your mind.
I kid you not,
and now they're all talking
about how we were fighting
in the AV room.
They honestly believe
we were having
a lover's quarrel.
I feel guilty
for freaking those two out.
Hey, Yuki?
Are you okay?
Uh, yeah.
I...
What?
Someone asked you out?
Mm-hmm.
Happened four days ago.
That long?
Don't leave him hanging.
It's been a minute
because I haven't figured out
how to turn him down!
You're not even gonna
give him a shot?
Well, of course not.
We're complete strangers.
Also,
he looks so serious
about everything he said.
I feel bad replying with a
sorry, dude,
but thanks for playing.
You know?
Mm...
Oh.
You could let him down easy
if you had a fake boyfriend.
Toadu!
No, he would hate that!
If you explain it,
he'll play along.
What makes you think he won't?
I don't know.
Uh-huh.
It's going down after school.
Yep.
See you then.
Ishikawa's officially in!
That was fast!
Alright.
So, what's the game plan?
Well,
I was thinking
while she's turning him down,
you could be busy
feeling her up.
Slow your roll there, Satan!
That's way too dirty!
Come on, Hori!
And what class is he in, anyway?
Class six, I think?
Yep.
And his name is Yanagi.
Before we do this, though,
am I the best fit?
Wouldn't you prefer,
I don't know,
someone who actually qualifies
as hot?
Well,
as far as looks are concerned,
I see you have Yanagi beat,
so you'll do just fine.
Okay.
But you only have him
beat by a hair!
My hair or his?
We should probably
get a move on.
Are you coming with us?
Heck yeah, I am!
It's bestie support time!
Thanks, Hori.
We doing this?
Um...
We're my girlfriend now, right?
Let's go.
I forget who's even in class six.
It's hard to remember
when you don't see him
all the time.
Maybe Ayasaki knows him?
Just for today.
All you have to do
is stand there.
I'll handle the talking.
You sure?
You agreed to help me out
with this,
so it's the least I can do.
It's a pretty big sacrifice.
But I wouldn't mind
if I got just one word in.
Something that sounds tough.
I'll be like,
she's mine, pal,
so keep your hands off.
Look, you're only supposed
to pretend to be my boyfriend!
That was pretend.
Whatever.
Chime in if you want to.
I can't hear a thing.
There he is.
Sorry I'm late, Yoshikawa.
Thanks for waiting.
I was held up by my teacher.
Holy crap, he's gorgeous!
He's a zillion times
hotter than Toru!
Come on!
Yeah, I am.
Hi.
Oh, nice to meet you.
I'm Akane Yanagi
from class six.
Sexy and a cool name!
Ishikawa from class one.
Not even Miyamoto
holds a candle
to the walking cover model
over here.
You can do this, Ishikawa.
I see.
You're taken.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I'm genetically inferior
on every level.
Hell, if he asked me
how I'd say yes in a heartbeat,
you should call us
out of her damn mind.
Guess it can't be helped.
Not only is he cool,
but your boyfriend's
clearly more attractive
than I am.
Take my dream already!
Well, best be on my way.
Oh, bye.
Yuki!
What?
You sidestepped a stud muffin?
No.
Well, yes.
But he's kind of too dreamy.
Plus, I think he's into fancy food.
And that's not my scene.
So she's a pleb.
For a split second,
I thought I had died
and went to heaven.
And he was a beautiful angel.
Who would have guessed
we had someone like that
in our grade
this whole time?
Remy knows him.
He's hot, huh?
And to top it up,
he's hilarious.
Hilarious how?
Yonaki, glasses.
Yeah, I haven't bought
a new pair yet.
But even without him,
I should...
There's a door there!
Happens more often
than you think.
Oh, wow.
His eyes are super bad,
but he's still cute.
He can't see?
Hey, wait!
Yes?
I think you mistook me
for somebody else.
Yeah, so like,
there's a girl named Kyoko Hori
I'm best friends with.
She's about this much taller than me
and prettier
by a mile.
Are you sure you didn't mean
to ask her out?
Why would you...
You must have talked
to one of my classmates
and found out
how bad my eyes are.
I had the right person.
I've liked you
for a while now,
so I know
what you look like.
I can't say the same
for this friend of yours, though.
Oh, uh...
Okay.
Yuki!
Hori!
I'm sorry.
Did I interrupt you?
Oh, hey, what's up, Yonaki?
You're Hori?
Yoshikawa was just
telling me about you.
Her very tall,
good-looking friend.
Or so she says.
I'm another friend,
Miyamura.
Oops, sorry.
I didn't realize
you were here too, Ishikawa.
I'm Hori.
What?
Then who might you be?
We literally met yesterday.
You'll have to forgive me,
uh, Miyamura.
His eyesight's
kinda on the fritz.
Gee, you think?
Oh, gosh!
I, uh...
You're probably wondering
why I'm with your girlfriend,
but I promised
we were just talking.
Huh?
Hey, Hori,
where did Ishikawa go?
Right here.
This is hilarious.
Sorry!
There's no need to panic, okay?
Anyway,
please believe me
when I say
nothing funny
happened between us.
Hell, man.
cool.
Thank you very much.
We'll be getting started with you tonight.
We'll beарunket.
Let's take care of that.
Again, I stated that one.
After I met this, I heard ya.
Well, as I woke up this morning,
you were masturbating tour and sit with youreed
Kizuta, kuyu no aasa da
Yakusok suru yo
Jikaku ni iru kara
Mire nahi mono hodo
Da iji ni suru yo
Koto ba ni deki nahiんだ kodo ne
Jika ni rica
Tumjaru